<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>

    <template id="report_employee_appointment">
        <t t-call="web.html_container">
            <t t-call="erpharbor_account_hr.report_layout">
                <div class="page" style="margin-right:45px;margin-left:45px;font-family:Liberation Serif;">
                    <t t-foreach="docs" t-as="doc">
                    <div class="oe_structure"/>
                    <center>
                        <u><h6><b>Appointment Letter</b></h6></u>
                    </center>
                    <div class="col-md-6" style="text-align:justify;">
                        Dear <b><span t-field="doc.employee_id.name"/></b>,<br/><br/>
                        We are pleased to inform you that on successful of your training &amp; probation, We have decided to
                        offer you a post of <b><span t-field="doc.job_id.name"/></b> with <b><span t-field="doc.company_id.name"/></b>. This is an
                        official letter confirming your employment with <b><span t-field="doc.company_id.name"/></b> starting on
                        <b><t t-if="doc.date_start"><span t-esc="doc.date_start.strftime('%d %B,%Y')"/></t></b><br/><br/>

                        Your employment is subject to the terms and conditions detailed in the contract document supplied
                        individually with this letter.<br/><br/>

                        Congratulations and welcome a board to <b><span t-field="doc.company_id.name"/></b>. Looking forward to
                        achieve many more milestones on this professional journey together.<br/><br/><br/><br/>

                        Sincerely,<br/><br/><br/><br/><br/>
                        Abhishek Mehta

                        <p style="page-break-after:always;"/><br/>
                        According to the terms of this agreement, <b><span t-field="doc.company_id.name"/></b>. will employee
                        <b>
                            <span t-field="doc.employee_id.name"/></b> position of <b><span t-field="doc.job_id.name"/></b> beginning on <b>
                            <t t-if="doc.date_start"><span t-esc="doc.date_start.strftime('%d %B,%Y')"/></t>
                        </b>.<br/><br/>

                        <b>1. Duties and Responsibilities:</b><br/><br/>
                        Develop new features and app that users care about. Under responsibility of Senior Odoo
                        Developer, analyze challenge and estimate customer requirements gathered by our business
                        analysts. Define features scope, bring a real value to the product. You will also get the chance to
                        contribute to the development of the company through your vision and your taste for entrepreneurial
                        activities.<br/><br/>

                        <b>2. Discipline:</b><br/><br/>
                        The employee should always be punctual and must give 100% to the copany and obey all the laws
                        as well as follow all the rules and regulation of the company. He/she should not breach the duty
                        assigned to them or any act of indiscipline or not following any conditions of the contract, he/she
                        will get punished as per the management discipline.<br/><br/>

                        <b>3. Compensation:</b><br/><br/>
                        The remuneration package offered to you for the said designation is <b><span t-field="doc.wage"/></b> <b>INR</b> Gross Per Month.
                        Your salary, incentives, allowances and / or any kind of payment / deductions, if any, will be subject
                        to the prevailing norms there under. The company will deduct <b><span t-field="doc.deduction"/></b> <b>INR</b> per month as <b>security
                        deposit</b> for one year and at the end of the year this deposit will be <b>refunded,</b> if left early then it will
                        not be payable. Pay schedule: The employee will be paid according to the organization’s established pay schedule i.e. from <b>5<sup>th</sup> to 15<sup>th</sup></b> of the respective month.<br/><br/>

                        <b>4. Place of work</b><br/><br/>
                        Your current place of work will be our official Address as shown in Letter. However, you may be
                        asked to work within India or outside India(onsite) for some amount of time, purely based on the.
                        work. The Company will provide working atmosphere as well as all facilities to
                        employees with adequate and necessary installation like computers having all required
                        software’s and facility needed as per the nature of work.<br/><br/>

                        <b>5. Increments</b><br/><br/>
                        Your increment(s) and future prospects in the company are totally dependent on how efficiently and
                        diligently you carry out the responsibilities levied on you. Other than your performance on job, your
                        regularity in attendance, sincerity, good conduct, company's performance and other such relevant
                        factors will be taken into consideration by the management. Employee's performance is reviewed
                        once a year.<br/><br/><br/>


                        <b>6. Work hours or schedule:</b><br/><br/>
                        The standard hours for organizations are <b>9 hrs</b> per day from Monday to Friday and 1st, 3rd &amp; 5th
                        Saturday. For now, 2nd &amp; 4th saturday will be holiday, The employee has to work
                        from Monday to Saturday as per the standard hours decided. In case of urgency employeer have right to
                        make changes in above.<br/><br/>

                        <b>7. Annual leave: </b><br/><br/>
                        Employee is entitled to annual leave i.e. vacation with pay in accordance with organization’s policy.
                        Employees can take 12 casual leaves on prorata basis during the year and that to with a prior notice
                        of at least 3-4 days.Sunday is a non working day and holiday in continuance to leave will be
                        regarded as casual leave and not holiday. Employee has to inform management in case of
                        emergency leave if not then there will be double deduction in salary.<br/><br/>

                        <b>8. Termination of contract:</b><br/><br/>
                        <b>By the employer with cause:</b> Under these circumstances <b>no compensation</b> will be paid. If the
                        employee breaches the contract or if the company is not satisfied with the work of the employee
                        then the contract will be terminated without any notice period.<br/><br/>
                        <b>By the employer without cause:</b> The employer will give <b>2 months written notice</b> to the employee
                        and pay salary and benefits in respect of the notice period as agree.<br/><br/>
                        <b>By the employee:</b> The employee will give <b>2 months written notice.</b> The employer will pay salary
                        and benefits in respect of the notice period as agreed.<br/><br/>
                        In case of <b>temporary employee</b> they are terminated at the end of contract period.<br/><br/>

                        <b>9. Privacy Policy:</b><br/><br/>
                        In any situation or condition there should be <b>no discussion regarding salary and increment.</b> If the
                        management will find you are not following rules there will be <b>strict action</b> will be taken by the
                        management in the above situation.<br/><br/>

                        <b>10. Discipline and Conduct</b><br/><br/>
                        During the course of your service you will discharge your duties efficiently and diligently and to the
                        best of your ability. You will devote your entire time and attention to the work of the Company and
                        will not undertake any direct/indirect business or work, honorary or remuneration except with the
                        written permission of the management in each case. Contravention of this will lead to termination of
                        your service without any notice or any compensation in lieu of such notice.<br/><br/>
                        The Company expects you to work with high standards of sincerity, efficiency, honesty and
                        integrity. During your employment term you shall diligently and faithfully carry out the instructions
                        given to you, in connection with the business and to the best of your skills, talent and ability,
                        improve and further the business interest of the Company. You shall not indulge in activities
                        detrimental to the interest of the Company.<br/><br/>
                        During your tenure with the Company you will not disclose, divulge, or make public any of our
                        technical, trade, professional or business data, process, product or software or any other important
                        information, which might come into your possession during the continuance of your appointment
                        with us. Your obligation to keep such information confidential shall remain even on termination or
                        cancellation of this employment.<br/><br/>
                        You will not, at any time, while in employment with the company, use other than reference to the
                        business of the company and in the course of your duties any such confidential information OR
                        after cessation of employment with the Company, use to disclose to anyone else such confidential
                        information and you will also undertake to indemnify the company and its affiliates from any loss
                        or damage from any breach of this undertaking.<br/><br/>
                        You will disclose to us forthwith any discovery invention, process or improvement made or
                        discovered by you while in the Company's service and such discovery, invention, process or
                        improvement shall belong absolutely to and be the sole property of the Company. You shall abide
                        by the code of ethics/conduct of the Company as existing from time to time.<br/>
                        You shall maintain proper discipline and dignity of the office and shall deal with all matter with
                        temperance. You shall communicate to the company any change in your address, as well as,
                        personal status. All communications sent to you in normal course to the address given by you shall
                        be deemed to have been received by you.<br/><br/><br/>

                        <b>11. Verification of documents</b><br/>
                        Your appointment is subject to verification of documents duly submitted by you regarding
                        qualification, experience, expertise etc. In case particulars mentioned in your application are found
                        false, not authentic or without documentary proof, your service would be liable to termination at
                        any time without a notice or any compensation in lieu thereof.<br/><br/>

                        <b>12. Others</b><br/><br/>
                        You may be required to undertake travel on company work as and when required. In case of travel
                        on company business, you will be entitled to such travel expenses/allowances as may be in force
                        from time to time.<br/>
                        You will be entitled to leave in accordance with the rules of the company, the details of which will
                        be intimated to you separately. You will abide by company policies, rules and regulations that are in
                        force for the time being or may be reframed from time to time.<br/><br/>
                        With best wishes!

                    </div>
                    </t>
                </div>
            </t>
        </t>
    </template>

    <template id="footer_address">
        <t t-foreach="docs" t-as="doc">
            <div style="width:100%;height:50px;">
                <b style="margin-left:20px;">
                    <span t-esc="doc.company_id.street"/>
                    <span t-esc="doc.company_id.street2"/>
                    <span t-esc="doc.company_id.city"/>
                    <span t-esc="doc.company_id.state_id.name"/>
                    <span t-esc="doc.company_id.country_id.name"/>
                    <span t-esc="doc.company_id.zip"/>
                </b><br/>
                <table class="table table-bordered"
                       style="border: 1px solid black;background-color:#00008B;color:white; margin-bottom: 0px;">
                    <tr>
                        <td style="padding:inherit;" width="30%" align="center">
                            <span t-esc="doc.company_id.phone"/>
                        </td>
                        <td style="padding:inherit;" width="30%" align="center">
                            <span t-esc="doc.company_id.email"/>
                        </td>
                        <td style="padding:inherit;border:1px solid #00008B;" width="60%" align="center">
                            <span t-esc="doc.company_id.website"/>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                </table>
            </div>
        </t>
    </template>

</odoo>